

Gheorghe Madalina-Eleonora

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Details

Bucharest

Romania

0768792728

madalinaeleonora.gheorghe@gmail.com

	ч		r	
ш	Г	ſ		7
	п			•

Personal Website

Linkedin

Medium

GitHub

500px

Skills

JavaScript

Vue

Angular

TypeScript

React

Ionic Framework

Git

Sass

Adobe Photoshop

Amazon AWS

Languages

English

Romanian

Profile

I gathered my passions in Web Development. I'm a Bucharest-based software engineer specialised in building (and occasionally designing) digital experiences. I work in a proactive way, every time ready to face challenges and working well under pressure. I am creative and my analytical thinking is helping me to find solutions for difficult situations.

Employment History

Consultant / Frontend Developer, Deloitte Digital, Bucharest

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

Overall technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REST, Angular, React, Thymeleaf, Mambu, TypeScript, AWS Services, Java

- Client 2: Germany (02.2022 Present) Banking
- Client 1: Alpha Team United Kingdom (10.2021 01.2022) Banking, Insurance

See details on website.

Frontend Developer, IBM Romania, Bucharest

DECEMBER 2018 - OCTOBER 2021

Overall technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REST, Sass, Angular, VirtualBox, Ionic, TypeScript, Capacitor, RxJs, React.js, Adobe Experience Manager

- Client 3: United States (04/2020 10/2021) E-Commerce
- Client 2: United Kingdom (03/2020 03/2020) Retail
- Client 1: Germany (03/2019 03/2020) Reinsurance

See details on website.

Internships

Matlab Database Practicant - Drive your future, Groupe Renault

JUNE 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2017

Overall technologies: SQL Database, Matlab, C#

Frontend Developer, IBM Romania

DECEMBER 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019

 $Overall\ technologies: \textbf{HTML}, \textbf{CSS}, \textbf{JavaScript}, \textbf{REST}, \textbf{Sass}, \textbf{Angular}, \textbf{Ionic}, \textbf{TypeScript}$

Education

Master's degree in Information Technology Administration and Management, Romanian-American University, Bucharest

OCTOBER 2018 - JULY 2020

Grade: **9.66**

Licentiate degree in Information Technology Administration and Management, Romanian-American University, Bucharest

OCTOBER 2015 - JULY 2018

Grade: 9.50

Certifications

Angular (Intermediate) - HackerRank

MARCH 2022

Link to certificate

Hobbies

Technology, Photography, Cars

Think Like a Hacker - IBM Romania

SEPTEMBER 2021

Link to badge

IBM Mentor - IBM Romania

DECEMBER 2020

Link to badge

JavaScript Front End Development - IBM Romania

DECEMBER 2020

Link to badge

IBM Agile Explorer - IBM Romania

MARCH 2020

Link to badge

Awards

2nd place at Rau-DevHack Hackathon

APRIL 2019

1st place at Web&Mobile Challenge at DevHacks

NOVEMBER 2018

Latest recommendation

Silvana-Roberta Helal, Senior Manager in Deloitte Digital

MAY 2022

"Madalina recently joined our team and rapidly adapted to the project specifics and pace. Feedback from both team and local technical lead is positive as Madalina started working on the project near stabilization phase, but managed to get familiar in a short timeframe with the complexity of the project [...]" See more on website.